it probably goes without saying but I'm
going to say it anyway you should be
having all of your conversations about
your development on any project in
GitHub not Discord not Reddit not slack
here's why there's a bunch of work and
changes that have happened here this is
a draft PR so therefore everybody knows
that it's not yet ready but it's under
work somebody makes somebody notices
something here as you can see they
detected I had bash completion just set
to look for bash in the Shell uh thing
and then I wasn't allowing completion
but shite has gotten completion to work
on Zell by adding a couple things from
it that are very basic a lot of people
do it and I'll show I'll do another
video about how to get bash completion
on zshell how to get compline completion
the comment says it's not important but
the comment says look for compline
instead and this is why you should put
all your comments in here the comment
the the actual change that that does
what was in the comment comes
immediately after the
conversation so the point I'm trying to
make is and by the way this doesn't have
to slow you down at all if you need to
make a comment you can do it right here
GPR
comment right I'm going to show you so
you hit entering with thanks I got that
into the last
commit you hit yes
and from the command line you can just
while you're doing your coding if you
have a thought if you if you want to
remember to come back to something if
you need to add a to-do to the to-do
list to the task list at the top you can
do all of that in line and it will be
visible to everybody who's monitoring
the project in a collaborative way so
they can see it happening if you don't
do that all that conversation is lost or
at you know best has to be associated
with the WR a conversation in Discord
that's all learn it love it it's great